[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 26]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
“Unsoiled Starlight” ]
[Original Author: Shan Gu Jun]
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm at my mom's.
Why didn't you come home?
My mom wanted to get out.
So I’ll spend a couple days with her.
It’ll also give me time to think.
Tinglan,
don't overthink it.
We'll be fine.
Yeah, I know.
By the way,
your dad...
Don't worry.
He's fine now.
That's good.
We'll be back tomorrow night.
I'll wait for you at home
and make you something delicious.
Okay.
Tinglan,
this place is really nice.
I chose it for you.
I guessed you'd like it.
I love it.
This way.
Okay.
Mom,
we'll stay here tonight.
Tinglan,
it's quite nice here.
There's even a yard.
Mom,
have a seat.
Okay.
I'll help you change your shoes.
Let's change the shoes.
What do you feel like for dinner?
Anything is fine. You decide.
Hello, Lawyer Xiao.
The trial is on Monday.
Familiarize yourself with the case files.
Let's try to win this battle.
Okay.
I'll sort it out right away.
Mom,
I have to work overtime.
When I'm done,
I'll take you out to eat,
okay?
Tinglan,
still working on a weekend?
Don’t overdo it.
I feel bad.
I finally have time to take you out,
but I still have to work.
Work comes first.
If you feel bored,
go for a walk in the yard.
Okay.
Please,
don't cause trouble for Tinglan.
don't make things hard for her.
Please!
Aunt Zhang.
Please get it straight.
I'm not causing trouble for Shu Tinglan.
But you are.
Poor mother, lowly daughter,
dreaming of marrying up
and rising to the top?
Does Shu Tinglan have what it takes?
Not to mention,
she's stuck with a mother like you.
She's just delusional.
I didn't!
I didn't affect Tinglan!
I didn't drag Tinglan down!
I...
I... I didn't...
I didn't burden Tinglan.
I didn't...
Hello, Lawyer Xiao.
Okay.
I'll send it to you in a bit.
I'm currently working
on the evidence
for the plaintiff's qualification.
Okay.
Tinglan,
I'm going out for a walk.
Okay.
Mom.
Take care.
And the analysis of the key issues
is not finished yet.
Okay.
Understood.
Yes.
Okay.
Mom?
Excuse me, sir.
Have you seen my mom?
She went to the stream,
looking for a little sweater.
Okay.
I see.
Thank you.
Mom?
Hey, Miss.
It's going to rain.
Mom?
Mom!
Uncle Zhuo,
I know what you're going to say.
But until Zhuo Yu'an agrees,
I won't agree to a divorce.
Miss Shu,
I know your love is strong.
But do you realize
this relationship was a mistake
from the start?
It's rotten to the core.
One day,
you'll destroy the Zhuo family
and destroy Zhuo Yu'an.
Since we chose each other,
we have to keep going
to find out
the outcome.
Young people are always naïve.
Fighting a losing battle
is always a thankless task.
In the end,
those without protection always get hurt.
Thanks for your concern.
But since I made my choice,
I don't care.
You don't care,
but what about the people around you?
Your mother, Zhang He.
friend Lin Zhihuan,
Your boss.
Your co-workers.
The ties in this world
are always more than you imagine.
[Divorce Agreement]
♪ A meteor crossed the promise we made ♪
♪ Memories fade at a touch ♪
Hello, Tinglan.
♪ Seasons turn and fade ♪
I'm cooking.
What would you like for dinner?
♪ I still feel your hand in mine ♪
Zhuo Yu'an…
♪ Time slips away ♪
Let's get a divorce.
♪ Regrets left unsaid rush in ♪
What happened?
♪ The warmth we shared ♪
♪ Still lives within ♪
♪ Back then, joy came far too easy ♪
♪ We knew how to waste it all ♪
♪ Before we learned to hold it tight ♪
♪ We let each other fall ♪
♪ One last time ♪
♪ I walked with you around that bend ♪
♪ A hug said all we couldn't say ♪
It's a pity
♪ We once had everything ♪
I can't cook now.
Otherwise,
♪ This time we lost our way ♪
I wouldn't let you get so thin.
♪ Don't forget me ♪
When you get better,
I'll make you cook for me.
♪ The wind blew us apart ♪
Five meals a day,
until you can't stand it.
Okay.
♪ We ran, we cried, we laughed as one ♪
It's my fault
for dragging you down.
♪ Walked through every twist and turn ♪
At such a young age,
you had to think everything through.
♪ Yet missed the happiness so near ♪
Neither of us
♪ Only after we've lost ♪
is a burden to the other.
♪ And can't touch again ♪
♪ Do we truly know what we had ♪
♪ We loved ♪
♪ Beneath the stars, we froze in time ♪
♪ Back then, joy came far too easy ♪
[Late Mother Zhang He]
♪ We knew how to waste it all ♪
♪ Before we learned to hold it tight ♪
Mom,
I failed you.
♪ We let each other fall ♪
♪ One last time ♪
I might not be able
♪ I walked with you around that bend ♪
to keep my promise.
♪ A hug said all we couldn't say ♪
I want to start over.
♪ We once had everything ♪
You won't blame me,
♪ This time we lost our way ♪
right?
♪ Don't forget me ♪
♪ The wind blew us apart ♪
♪ We ran, we cried, we laughed as one ♪
♪ Walked through every twist and turn ♪
♪ Yet missed the happiness so near ♪
♪ Only after we've lost ♪
♪ And can't touch again ♪
Tinglan?
♪ Do we truly know what we had ♪
♪ We loved ♪
♪ Beneath the stars, we froze in time ♪
[Divorce Agreement]
♪ The wind blew us apart ♪
♪ We ran, we cried, we laughed as one ♪
♪ Walked through every twist and turn ♪
[Divorce Agreement]
♪ Yet missed the happiness so near ♪
♪ Only after we've lost ♪
♪ And can't touch again ♪